<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Proxyman</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_title">⚠️ Important Legal Disclaimer</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_text">LEGAL DISCLAIMER AND TERMS OF USE\n\nBy using Proxyman for Android, you acknowledge and agree to the following:\n\n1. AUTHORIZED USE ONLY\nThis application is designed for network debugging and analysis purposes. You must ONLY use this application on domains, networks, and systems for which you have EXPLICIT WRITTEN PERMISSION from the owner.\n\n2. PROHIBITION OF UNAUTHORIZED INTERCEPTION\nIntercepting, monitoring, or capturing network traffic on domains or systems without proper authorization is ILLEGAL in most jurisdictions and may violate federal and state laws including but not limited to:\n• The Computer Fraud and Abuse Act (CFAA)\n• The Electronic Communications Privacy Act (ECPA)\n• The Wiretap Act\n• Similar laws in your jurisdiction\n\n3. MITM (Man-in-the-Middle) FUNCTIONALITY\nThis application includes MITM proxy capabilities that can intercept HTTPS traffic. This feature must ONLY be used:\n• On your own devices and networks\n• On systems you own or have written authorization to test\n• For legitimate software development and debugging purposes\n• In compliance with all applicable laws and regulations\n\n4. USER RESPONSIBILITY\nYou are solely responsible for ensuring that your use of this application complies with all applicable laws, regulations, and agreements. The developers of this application assume NO LIABILITY for any misuse.\n\n5. NO WARRANTY\nThis application is provided \"AS IS\" without warranty of any kind. The developers are not responsible for any damages resulting from the use or misuse of this application.\n\n6. ACCEPTANCE\nBy checking the box below and tapping \"I Accept\", you confirm that you understand these terms and agree to use this application only for authorized purposes.</string>
    <string name="accept_checkbox_text">I understand and agree that I will ONLY use this application on domains and systems for which I have explicit authorization</string>
    <string name="accept_button">I Accept</string>
    <string name="decline_button">I Decline</string>
    <string name="empty_traffic">No traffic captured yet.\nTap the play button to start intercepting.</string>
</resources>
